The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
It's been a while,
Brother Ceng Niu is still as graceful as before.
Mo Zhi
Envoy of the Cultivation Alliance
Brother Mo Zhi.
Yes, it's me.
You, step back.
I have a question,
I hope Brother Ceng Niu can answer it.
Why did you
refuse to become the next Suzaku ?
So that's how it is...
It's not that the Cultivation Planet Crystal chose me
but rather...
he chose me.
My ambitions
are higher than planet Suzaku.
It's a shame...
Since Brother Ceng Niu made up his mind,
then I will not try to persuade you.
Repair.
This is the Cultivation Planet Heart.
The one who obtains it,
becomes the next Suzaku.
The Cultivation Planet Heart...
But my cultivation is too low...
The one who obtains it can directly become the Suzaku ?
Middle stage Soul Transformation ?
How did her cultivation increase so drastically ?
No...
This aura...
It's Qian Feng !
A cultivation furnace
that was able to reverse her fate ?
How rare...
Azure Dragon bloodline,
you are also a qualified candidate.
Unfortunately,
you are not Soul Transformation
so you won't be respected.
In that case,
the next Suzaku shall be...
Brother Mo, wait a minute.
Although he hasn’t reached Soul Transformation,
that doesn’t mean he never will.
Wang Lin,
what do you mean by that ?
What does Brother Mo think ?
Wang Lin !
Your Billion-Soul Flag is useless now
and you are just Early stage Soul Transformation.
If I want to kill you,
it would be as easy as waving my hand !
And if I agree to become the next Suzaku ?
You !
Brother Ceng Niu, have you...
changed your mind ?
Do you really need to ask ?
Even if I become the Suzaku,
I would just pass the title
to him.
Interesting...
In that case,
from now on,
you are the 15th generation Suzaku.
I hope you will cultivate diligently here,
and properly comprehend the Suzaku Seal.
Forsaken Immortal Clan,
I can give you a third of planet Suzaku.
But every thousand years,
you must deliver at least a 9-Leaf's skull.
Yunque Zi,
do you agree ?
It's decided.
Thank you.
It's nothing,
you don't need to thank me.
Brother Ceng Niu,
I may need your help in the future.
I hope you will not refuse then.
Naturally.
I must now return to the Cultivation Alliance to report,
would Brother Ceng Niu like to leave with me ?
I still have some matters to deal with.
Use your celestial spiritual energy in this seal
and you can leave.
Brother Ceng Niu,
the path of immortality is long.
I hope that
we will meet again.
I have obtained both my and Wan'er's soul strand.
No one can control our lives anymore.
The Billion-Soul Flag is greatly weakened.
After I leave,
I need to find enough souls to repair it.
The next Suzaku is Zhou Wutai.
He is a grateful and righteous man.
Even if I leave,
he will take good care of my acquaintances.
That means
I no longer need to worry about them.
Xu Liguo.
Master,
I have tamed this half-moon blade.
It's very obedient.
This half-moon blade is pretty mysterious.
I'm sure it will be useful.
Number Four,
come and greet Master.
Greetings,
Master...?
This half-moon blade is hard to tame,
I can't even imprint my Divine Sense on it.
But somehow, it really likes Xu Liguo...
Alright,
as long as I can control it indirectly
and make it serve me.
Number Four, let's go !
1 year later
Falling from the night sky
and melting into dust
like water without a source.
Like the difference between clouds and mud,
the truth cannot be found in conflict.
Life and death
are like the moment when the rain falls.
And like many other unseparable things.
In this lifetime,
to cultivate the truth, cultivate the world first.
Old grudges had to be settled
because half an inch is engraved into my tree rings.
Use the most vivid love and hate
to ask questions to your fate.
Let your eyes be filled enough with rage
to pierce the heart and the soul
then soften because of the mortals' fireworks.
Only when you bend
can you understand the hidden edge of the blade.
The human mind is nature,
the rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,
there are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart
to depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.
After struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.
Everywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined
by this endless world.
Snow falls as my hair turns white, winter withers
while prosperity sprouts in summer.
I step into the world, with light at my fingertips,
the law of cause and effect.
I observe the vastness of heaven and earth
so I can get rid of evil.
Obsession arises from one thought, life and death arise from one thought.
Reincarnation is not to be feared.
Over the past year,
the Forsaken Immortal Clan retreated to the northwest of planet Suzaku.
From now on, they will no longer bother the cultivators.
After this war,
more than half of planet Suzaku's cultivators died.
Most sects and countries are severely weakened.
The Forsaken Immortal Clan retreated,
we have driven them away !
This is great, we won !
Zhou Wutai knew that he needed to be respected.
So right after leaving the Suzaku Tomb,
he went into seclusion on Mount Suzaku.
As for Zi Xin and Liu Mei,
I heard that both of them flew into the starry sky.
I wanted to recover the 4th primary soul that Zhuque Zi stole,
but I wasn't able to find it.
Little Ru'er is luckier than me.
At least she has a home to return to
and a chance to live with her parents.
If Little Ru'er ever cultivates to Nascent Soul,
Tie Yan will give this to her.
Before leaving,
I went to the old country of Xue Yue.
Even in this bitter cold,
I still found
flowers blooming.
Finally,
I returned to the place where I was born.
My son, it doesn't matter if you are not chosen.
Tie Zhu, you really look like an Immortal now.
You can always come back.
Noooo !!!
Father...
Mother...
Your son is going to leave…
Country of Zhou
Rank 4 cultivation country
Keep playing music !
Keep dancing !
Your Highness,
let me dance another song for you.
Situ,
it's time to go.
That was too quick...
Little Lin,
do you want to know why I cultivate ?
Let me tell you,
I cultivate because I want all treasures and women
of this world to be mine !
If I didn't keep running into strong enemies,
that forced me to cultivate to beat them,
I would have quit
cultivating long ago !
Situ,
your Dao and mine are different.
Let's go.
Let's make our own cultivation country.
Fool...
This is the cloud barrier.
After we cross it,
we will have left planet Suzaku.
Original body,
come !
Good !
Like this, you are Peak Middle stage Soul Transformation !
Disperse for me !
Brother Wang,
have a safe journey.
The younger generations will always surpass us...
Uncle ?
Goodbye, Ancestor !
Not bad,
at this speed
we will reach
the trade planet in a month.
Right,
I almost forgot this.
While you were gone,
I took a stroll around Forsaken Immortal Clan
and picked up a bunch of these things.
It's for you, take them.
Thank you.
You're going to planet Tian Yun, right ?
You must get ready.
After watching you fight,
I think you rely too much on artifacts.
Your spells aren't that good...
Since that's the case,
I will teach you 3 spells !
I created these 3 spells
with my insights after thousands of years of cultivation.
Their power is unmatched.
Wang Lin,
you're the only person I will ever pass these to !
Death Finger !
Demonic Finger !
These are...
demonic flames ?
This is the final move...
Little Lin,
watch closely !
Underworld Finger !
Let's go,
spar with me.
Let me see how much you've learned !
1 month later
Not bad, not bad.
I don't need to worry about you now.
If you want to know something else,
ask me now.
Situ,
what is there
after Ascendant ?
Cultivators embarking on the path of immortality
all believe that cultivation begins with Qi Condensation
and ends with Ascendant.
But they don't realize
that this is merely the first step.
Above this...
there is a second step.
The second step ?
Exactly !
Ye Wuyou and I obtained this information from the Cultivation Alliance back then.
The second step
is called the 3 realms of Nirvana Shattering:
Nirvana Scryer,
Nirvana Cleanser,
and finally Nirvana Shatterer.
These realms
are the path beyond Ascendant.
Is your cultivation
Nirvana Scryer ?
It's not that easy.
Before the second step,
there are still two trials:
Illusory Yin an Corporeal Yang.
A cultivator's domain
will be tempered by the Illusory Yin and Corporeal Yang stages.
Only then will you be able to enter Nirvana Scryer.
We've arrived.
No matter what materials you need,
this trade planet
will definitely have them !
Trade Planet
Alliance Star System
Little Lin,
I'm going ahead
to plunder to my heart's content !
You can look around by yourself,
let's meet in 3 days.
I hope that this trade planet
has materials to refine my Star Compass.
Ming Mei City
Trade Planet
Feel free to pick whatever you like.
I thought it would take more effort
to buy this Void Wood Stone.
Void Wood Stone
This trade planet is pretty convenient.
I just need some Snow Ink,
but I can't find it anywhere.
Shang clan’s shop
I heard this Shang clan's shop claims to have everything.
Maybe they have some...
Stop right here !
You !
This is a place for nobles.
Who the hell are you ?
Get out of here !
A fight started !
Such fast attacks,
look !
Young Master, save me !
Stop.
Star Rotation !
Note: this is another spell Situ Nan taught that wasn't shown.
You actually ruined my cultivation foundation !
Bai Wei
Heavenly Fate Sect Purple Division disciple
Middle stage Soul Transformation
It's already over...
Impressive spell, Brother.
May I know what your name is ?
Wang Lin.
Wang Lin...
I am Bai Wei.
Young Master,
kill him !
Brother Wang,
my servant was rude.
Please don't be offended.
I am from planet Tian Yun,
a disciple of the Heavenly Fate Sect.
May I ask where Brother Wang is from ?
I'm a rogue cultivator
without a sect or planet.
Since Brother Wang is unwilling to speak,
then I will not inquire any further.
My master celebrates his birthday every 10 000 years and it's very soon.
If Brother Wang has time,
please come to planet Tian Yun
and allow me to be your host.
Young master, have a look.
So expensive !
Snow Ink
In Ming Mei City
at the Shang clan's shop,
I want the Snow Ink.
Stop running !
Stop this !
Come on, come on !
Thief, return my Snow Ink !
I'm not some young lady,
why are you idiots chasing after me ?
You're not getting away !
Here, Snow Ink.
Little Lin...
I'm leaving.
You can finally live like a king.
I'm sure we'll meet again...
That's right !
I'm going to enjoy the rest of my life
to the fullest.
A celestial artifact !?
And it's infinitely close to middle grade ?
Kid, how did you obtain so many treasures ?
This is...
the method to control this celestial artifact ?
Little Lin,
are you giving me this God Slaying Chariot ?
What ?
You don't want it ?
Who said I didn't want it !?
Wang Lin,
planet Tian Yun is filled with strangers,
be careful.
However, you can’t forget your pride as a cultivator of planet Suzaku.
If you have any problems,
come find me on planet Feng Luan.
With this old man around,
no one will dare to mess with you !
Don't get ahead of yourself.
If you ever get your ass kicked,
come find me on planet Tian Yun.
With me around,
no one will dare to touch you !
Keep that mentality !
Fine,
if I'm ever in trouble,
I'll come and find you.
You better make a name for yourself !
Because I'll be ashamed
if you don't.
Wang Lin,
take care.
I wonder if
we will have another chance to meet.
Situ,
take care.
I, Wang Lin, have never in my life
bowed to the heavens or the earth.
I pay respects to neither ghosts or gods.
I only bow to my parents
and pay respects to Situ...
There is an after credits scene.
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.
Wang Lin...
Next time,
you definitely
won't escape my grasp !